<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Simon&#39;s Blog on Simon Schraeder - Personal Blog</title>
    <link>https://simon-schraeder.de/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Simon&#39;s Blog on Simon Schraeder - Personal Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 13:05:38 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://simon-schraeder.de/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>andChill: Building an Alexa Skill with Spotify and Hue</title>
      <link>https://simon-schraeder.de/posts/andchill-building-alexa-skill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 13:05:38 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simon-schraeder.de/posts/andchill-building-alexa-skill/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve bought an Amazon Echo Dot as an entry into voice-controlling my home and I quite like it. It reacts fast enough, the voice recognition is good and it works beautifully with my Phillips Hue Lamps.
There is just one thing missing that annoys me: No macros. Often I&amp;rsquo;m coming home late in the evening and just want some music to play and the lights to be turned on. The voice recognicion is good, but it get&amp;rsquo;s tiring to say &amp;ldquo;Alexa, play Spotify playlist evening&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Alexa, turn on the bedroom lights on scene Evening&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://simon-schraeder.de/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2017 19:41:40 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simon-schraeder.de/contact/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy
English Thanks for your interest. You can reach me through the following ways. I&amp;rsquo;ll get back to you as soon as possible:
Email:
info@simon-schraeder.de
Mail
Simon Schraeder A306 Ernsthaldenstr. 47 70565 Stuttgart Germany  Mobile
(+49) 1575 7031306
Twitter
@der_simon
German Impressum
Angaben gemäß § 5 TMG:
Simon Schraeder A306 Ernsthaldenstr. 47 70565 Stuttgart Germany
Kontakt:
Telefon: +49 (0) 1575 7031306 Telefax: - E-Mail: info@simon-schraeder.de Verantwortlich für den Inhalt nach § 55 Abs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://simon-schraeder.de/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2017 19:41:40 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simon-schraeder.de/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Data protection is of a particularly high priority for me. The use of the Internet pages of Simon Schraeder is possible without any indication of personal data; however, if a data subject wants to use special enterprise services via our website, processing of personal data could become necessary. If the processing of personal data is necessary and there is no statutory basis for such processing, we generally obtain consent from the data subject.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Encrypt on Uberspace with Ghost</title>
      <link>https://simon-schraeder.de/posts/lets-encrypt-uberspace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2015 19:28:52 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simon-schraeder.de/posts/lets-encrypt-uberspace/</guid>
      <description>I haven&amp;rsquo;t really published a lot of blog posts in a long time due to time constraints and this post will be quite short as well.
Just wanted to give some pointers for people using the awesome webhost Uberspace who want to secure their site with Let&amp;rsquo;s Encrypt, especially when using Ghost. I was using Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s SSL before, but it felt kind of wrong to have a third-party MITM your requests to serve them over HTTPS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrape Webpages With JSDOM</title>
      <link>https://simon-schraeder.de/posts/scrape-webpages-with-jsdom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 19:49:12 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simon-schraeder.de/posts/scrape-webpages-with-jsdom/</guid>
      <description>A few days ago I took part in the &amp;ldquo;Data Münster Hackathon&amp;rdquo;, the kickoff event of a usergroup/meetup here in Muenster. It was a three day long hackaton (1 day of coding), which I won together with a colleague (recieved an iPad Air 2 :) ).
So together with a friend I knew from &amp;ldquo;Code For Muenster&amp;rdquo;, a meetup where we work on open data problems (my projects are on GitHub we decided to work on a logo parser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Imgur Redirects Direct Images</title>
      <link>https://simon-schraeder.de/posts/imgur-redirects-direct-images/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2014 19:49:44 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simon-schraeder.de/posts/imgur-redirects-direct-images/</guid>
      <description>Imgur is a popular hoster for images used on sites like twitter or reddit. To share the imag, you have the choice between using a hotlink to the file or using an url which shows the image along with ads.
But when you use the hotlink on Twitter, it seems like imgur automatically redirects to the website.
I decided to investigate this, which turned out to be quite simple.
First let&amp;rsquo;s see what imgur responds to a normal requests to the file:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Better UI: Display passwords</title>
      <link>https://simon-schraeder.de/posts/better-ui-display-password/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2013 19:50:20 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://simon-schraeder.de/posts/better-ui-display-password/</guid>
      <description>Signup for one service and one common thing you&amp;rsquo;ll see is a masked password box. This provides security because bystanders can&amp;rsquo;t read the password. It comes with a downside though: Your user will be annoyed if he makes a typo. This is especially annoying if the password needs to be typed two times to prevent typos and you have to type both passwords again.
But there is a simple solution to this problem: Provide an &amp;ldquo;unmask&amp;rdquo; function.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>